Washingtoniana Slide Collection P026 P026
Test
- Series 8: Truax Slideshows
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Streetcar, undated (Item 6352)
      Crowd around streetcar headed toward Mt. Rainier (Photographer: Unknown)
    - City View, undated (Item 6353)
      View of city and undeveloped land (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Harewood Hospital (Harewood Hospital), undated (Item 6354)
      Postcard sketch of Harewood Hospital, grounds and tents (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Bicycles, undated (Item 6355)
      Unicycle and bicycles parked on city street (Photographer: Unknown)
    - City Street, undated (Item 6356)
      City street, streetcar, cars and buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Wagon, undated (Item 6357)
      Man on horse-drawn wagon on city street (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Don't Shoot, undated (Item 6358)
      Man in car with sign in window, "Don't Shoot! No Liquor in this Car" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Payphone, undated (Item 6359)
      Man on payphone on crowded sidewalk (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Market, undated (Item 6360)
      People looking at produce (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Blue Mouse, undated (Item 6361)
      Blue Mouse Theater (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Capitol and Washington Monument), undated (Item 6362)
      Page from pamphlet(?) for Cherry Blossom Festival (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Washington Monument), undated (Item 6363)
      Cartoon of two children looking at advertisements (Photographer: Clifford Barryman, Illustrator)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), undated (Item 6364)
      Close-up of cherry blossom, car in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1922 (Item 6365)
      Two women with cherry tree (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1925 (Item 6366)
      Woman painting at easel among cherry trees (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Potomac Park), 1927 (Item 6367)
      Print of painting, "Potomac Park Cherry Trees, A Gift from Japan" (Photographer: Lesley Jackson)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1947 (Item 6368)
      View of Jefferson Memorial, cherry trees in bloom, traffic (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1947 (Item 6369)
      Cherry blossom trees, Jefferson Memorial at night (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1954 (Item 6370)
      Cover of pamphlet for 1954 National Cherry Blossom Festival (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1954 (Item 6371)
      Japanese woman with sculpture, surrounded by crowd (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1958 (Item 6372)
      Man putting crown on woman (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, 1958 (Item 6373)
      Women from 50 states and pageant winner (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1958 (Item 6374)
      Winner of Cherry Blossom Festival pageant being crowned, with three men (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1960 (Item 6375)
      Man and woman looking at cherry blossoms at night, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1962 (Item 6376)
      Uniformed man on horseback amidst cherry trees, Jefferson Memorial in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), 1962 (Item 6377)
      Woman's magnified eyes examining cherry blossoms with magnifying glass (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), Ca. 1917 (Item 6378)
      Children with baskets for Easter Egg Roll (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), 1927 (Item 6379)
      Print of painting, "The White House Easter Monday Egg Rolling" (Photographer: Lesley Jackson)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), 1938 (Item 6380)
      Eleanor Roosevelt holding hand of young girl, surrounded by crowd (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, 1940 (Item 6381)
      Crowd surrounding men in red uniforms on city street (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), 1941 (Item 6382)
      President Franklin Roosevelt greeting crowd from balcony (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Capitol), 1946 (Item 6383)
      Children on lawn with Easter baskets (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, 1951 (Item 6384)
      Five women wearing "Home Show" ribbons, sitting on top of convertible (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, 1951 (Item 6385)
      Five girls, a woman and a man standing shortest to tallest on city sidewalk (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, 1952 (Item 6386)
      Two women wearing decorated hats (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), 1958 (Item 6387)
      View from behind of Mamie and President Eisenhower greeting crowd from balcony (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), 1959 (Item 6388)
      Children in bunny costumes with giant Easter basket on lawn (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy SlideshowJerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), 1978 (Item 6389)
      Young girl sitting on lawn with Easter basket (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), 1981 (Item 6390)
      Spiderman and other superheroes greeting Nancy Reagan (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (White House), 1981 (Item 6391)
      Easter eggs decorated with patriotic themes and names: George Bush, Barbara Bush, Rick Nelson, Nancy Reagan, Ronald Reagan (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, Ca. 1910 (Item 6392)
      President Woodrow Wilson shaking hands with baseball player in front of audience (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, 1946 (Item 6393)
      President Woodrow Wilson throwing ball, surrounded by crowd; Babe Ruth on right (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, 1969 (Item 6394)
      President Richard Nixon throwing baseball, surrounded by crowd at Senators game (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Ford's Theatre), undated (Item 6395)
      "Old Ford's Theatre" and bicycle repair shop nextdoor (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Ford's Theatre), undated (Item 6396)
      Theatrical reinactment of Lincoln assassination (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Ford's Theatre), undated (Item 6397)
      Man holding and aiming pistol (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Ford's Theatre), undated (Item 6398)
      Girl and boy behind rocking chair (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, undated (Item 6399)
      Two men holding portrait of George Washington (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, undated (Item 6400)
      Woman and man holding boots in front of statue of Lincoln (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Petersen House, 516 10th Street NW), undated (Item 6401)
      House in which Abraham Lincoln died (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Petersen House, 516 10th Street NW), undated (Item 6402)
      Three men over bed in room in which Lincoln died (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Petersen House, 516 10th Street NW), undated (Item 6403)
      Man over bed (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Capitol?), undated (Item 6404)
      Statue of Lincoln, casket, mourners (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Petersen House, 516 10th Street NW), undated (Item 6405)
      Man dressed as Lincoln looking at sign, "In this house President Lincoln died…" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, undated (Item 6406)
      Funeral procession, train, casket draped in flag (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 6407)
      View of funeral procession, troops marching, casket (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 6408)
      Mourners crying (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, 1945 April 20 (Item 6409)
      Men and band on baseball field, crowd in stands (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow, undated (Item 6410)
      Two men and one woman over Franklin Roosevelt memorial (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jerry A. McCoy Slideshow (Tidal Basin), undated (Item 6411)
      Jefferson Memorial, cherry blossoms (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6412)
      Cover page from "Historical Court Records of Washington, District of Columbia", Vol. 14 (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6413)
      Page from book of "General Thomas addressing the Negroes of Louisiana on the duties of freedom"; Sketch of crowd (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6414)
      Page listing prices of various foods (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6415)
      Page on "Numbering Houses" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, 1887 October 6 (Item 6416)
      Certificate of "Freedom of the City of Washington" for Alexander R. Shepherd (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, 1911 January 7 (Item 6417)
      Receipt from Becker's Leather Goods Co. (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts (Howard University), 1891 September 18 (Item 6418)
      Document with sketch of building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, 1889 February 5 (Item 6419)
      Document from American Telephone Company; Sketch of building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6420)
      "#1 Building - Opened in 1927" (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6421)
      District Training School label (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6422)
      Dunbar Drug Store building, advertisements in windows (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6423)
      Card catalog records for deaths in 1913 (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6424)
      Page from Washington Street Directory (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6425)
      Map legend with symbols for "Eliminated Houses, Eliminated Pestholes, Degraded Negroes, Suspicious Houses, Not Public Houses, Under Surveillance" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, 1913 January 7 (Item 6426)
      "Kenyon Act"; Cover page of Abatement of Houses of Ill Fame (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6427)
      Page showing death records of Washington, DC, 1801-1878 (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6428)
      Cover page of "Death Records of Washington, DC, 1801-1878" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, undated (Item 6429)
      Page showing marriage records of Washington, DC (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ghosts, 1897 March 4 (Item 6430)
      Cover of invitation(?) to Inaugural Ball, March 4, 1897; Image of building, red ribbon (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Three Sisters Islands, Potomac River), undated (Item 6431)
      View of islands, building in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Three Sisters Islands, Potomac River), undated (Item 6432)
      View of islands, Georgetown in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Halcyon House, 3400 Prospect Street NW), undated (Item 6433)
      Doorway, ivy-covered walls (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Prospect House, 3508 Prospect Street NW), undated (Item 6434)
      View from street (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Admiral Weaver House, 2823 N Street NW), undated (Item 6435)
    - Washington Ghosts (Old Stone House), undated (Item 6436)
    - Washington Ghosts (Key Mansion), undated (Item 6437)
      Top half of decorated mansion (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Pan American Union Building), undated (Item 6438)
      Front of building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Van Ness Mansion), undated (Item 6439)
      People on roof, porch (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Oak Hill Cemetery), undated (Item 6440)
      Van Ness Mausoleum (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Washington Ghosts (Octagon House), undated (Item 6441)
    - Washington Ghosts (Octagon House), undated (Item 6442)
      Oval stairwell (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Marine Commander House), Ca. 1970 (Item 6443)
      House and other building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Woodrow Wilson House), undated (Item 6444)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6445)
      Portait of President Woodrow Wilson (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (White House), 1860 (Item 6446)
      Colored sketch (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6447)
      Portait of President James Garfield (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (White House), undated (Item 6448)
      Lincoln Bedroom (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (White House), undated (Item 6449)
      Rose Room (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (White House), undated (Item 6450)
      Yellow Oval Room (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (White House), undated (Item 6451)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6452)
      Portrait of Abigail Adams (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (White House), undated (Item 6453)
      Sketch of East Room (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6454)
      Portrait of John Wilkes Booth (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Ford's Theatre), undated (Item 6455)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6456)
      Portrait of Mary Surratt, "Conspirators" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Surratt House), undated (Item 6457)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6458)
      Portrait of General Joseph Holt (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6459)
      Portrait of President Abraham Lincoln (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Oak Hill Cemetery), undated (Item 6460)
      William Thomas Carroll Tomb (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Washington Ghosts (Oak Hill Cemetery), undated (Item 6461)
    - Washington Ghosts (Rock Creek Cemetery), undated (Item 6462)
      "Grief" statue (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Lafayette Square), undated (Item 6463)
      Statue and surrounding buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6464)
      Portrait of Dolly Madison (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Washington Club/Rodgers House), undated (Item 6465)
      Sketch of Washington Club (later Rodgers House) at right (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (St. John's Church), undated (Item 6466)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6467)
      Portrait of Stephen Decatur (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Decatur House), undated (Item 6468)
    - Washington Ghosts (Capitol), Ca. 1850 (Item 6469)
      Sketch of Capitol, people on street below (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6470)
      Portrait of Major Pierre L'Enfant (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6471)
      Portrait of President John Quincy Adams (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Capitol), undated (Item 6472)
      Statuary Hall (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Capitol), undated (Item 6473)
    - Washington Ghosts (Capitol), undated (Item 6474)
      Rotunda (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Capitol), undated (Item 6475)
      Library of Congress (in Capitol) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Supreme Court Building), undated (Item 6476)
    - Washington Ghosts (Old Capitol), undated (Item 6477)
      Old brick Capitol (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Old Pension Office), undated (Item 6478)
      View of building, grounds (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Old Pension Office), undated (Item 6479)
      Simulated marble columns (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (Smithsonian Castle), undated (Item 6480)
      "Old Castle" (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6481)
      Hope Diamond (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts, 1939 (Item 6482)
      Mrs. Evelyn Walsh McLean and daughter (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (2020 Massachusetts Avenue NW), undated (Item 6483)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6484)
      Hope Diamond in someone's hand (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts (National Theatre), 1868 (Item 6485)
      People on balcony, sidewalk (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Washington Ghosts, undated (Item 6486)
    - Performance, undated (Item 6487)
      Girls in robes performing for small crowd (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ring Games, 1906 (Item 6488)
      "Ring Games Playground Tournament 1906"; Children playing on field, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Relay Race, undated (Item 6489)
      Plaque, "Relay Race Championship, P.S.A.M., 115 Lbs Class" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Division Champs, undated (Item 6490)
      Plaque, "Div. Championship, Elementary School Games, Georgetown Playground" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Band, undated (Item 6491)
      "Industrial Home School Band"; Ten boys with instruments (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6492)
      Children playing on playground (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6493)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6494)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6495)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6496)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6497)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6498)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6499)
      Children watching two women with rackets (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6500)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6501)
      Children standing in line, some wearing paper hats (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6502)
      Girls playing baseball (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6503)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6504)
      Barefoot girl in field (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6505)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6506)
      Woman and children standing in line (Photographer: Unknown)
    - People, undated (Item 6507)
      Man, baby and woman (Photographer: Unknown)
    - People, undated (Item 6508)
      Woman waering large hat, two men (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6509)
    - Fountain, undated (Item 6510)
      Boys playing in fountain, others watching (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Class Photo, undated (Item 6511)
      Group photo, about 60 children (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6512)
      Girls playing with rackets (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6513)
      Woman standing in group of seated children (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6514)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6515)
      Girls playing baseball, others watching (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Irish Dance (Rosedale), undated (Item 6516)
      "Rosedale Playground Irish Dance"; Group photo of children and adults (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6517)
      Nine boys and girls next to fence (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball, undated (Item 6518)
      Two boys, four men standing with wreath, "Walter Johnson Baseball League" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball (Griffith Stadium), undated (Item 6519)
      Men playing baseball in stadium (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball, undated (Item 6520)
      Man in baseball cap (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Band, undated (Item 6521)
      Men in band uniform with instruments (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Bucket, undated (Item 6522)
      Boy with head dunked in bucket of water (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball Team, undated (Item 6523)
      Baseball team photo; Men in N.B.R.A. uniforms (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball (Griffith Stadium), undated (Item 6524)
      Baseball player throwing ball; boy and others watch from dugout (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball (Griffith Stadium), undated (Item 6525)
      Baseball player throwing ball; boy watches from sidelines (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball (Griffith Stadium), undated (Item 6526)
      Baseball player with catcher's mit (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Football, undated (Item 6527)
      Boys with football, swingsets in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6528)
    - Boats, undated (Item 6529)
      Boys watching toy boats in pool (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6530)
      Children on playground, view between two trees (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6531)
      Boys knee deep in water (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6532)
      Boys and girls knee deep in water (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6533)
      Girls seated outside, working on embroidery (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6534)
      Children in lines, some walking through water (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6535)
      Children playing on playground, houses in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6536)
      Two girls standing outside fence, view from behind (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6537)
      Two girls and one boy standing outside fence, view from behind (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Class Photo, undated (Item 6538)
      Group photo of children (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6539)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6540)
      Children standing in lines (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - People, undated (Item 6541)
      Children and adults (Photographer: Unknown)
    - People, undated (Item 6542)
      Boys and women in field, houses in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - People, undated (Item 6543)
      Woman holding one end of ribbon, women, boys (Photographer: Unknown)
    - People, undated (Item 6544)
      Man in hat, surrounded by women and boys (Photographer: Unknown)
    - People, undated (Item 6545)
      Girls and boys in field, houses in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Alley, undated (Item 6546)
      Boys playing in alley (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball (Griffith Stadium), undated (Item 6547)
      Pitcher and umpire on pitcher's mound (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball (Griffith Stadium), undated (Item 6548)
      Three baseball players in field, one throwing ball (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball (Griffith Stadium), undated (Item 6549)
      Baseball player talking to umpires, surrounded by other players (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Baseball (Griffith Stadium), undated (Item 6550)
      Pitcher at mound (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6551)
      Children on seesaw (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6552)
      Line of girls with hands on shoulders (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6553)
      Girls playing on playground (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Children, undated (Item 6554)
      Girls and boys in line, some seated in trailer (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6555)
      Girls on slide (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Playground, undated (Item 6556)